Hey Hello guys so welcome to my channel, today is a
day of great news, today I feel
that I am going to get Ola very soon
and yesterday I got an email related to insurance,
so I have got the insurance policy of such a body, that is
like the previous one and Khana Jyotish and I did
not get it from any other side, but the thing is that when
I went and checked it, I can
see the insurance policy there, so
I forwarded it, there is an
option to forward it to your friends
and today in the morning I got a call from Ola
registration, you got two OTPs,
one was for Aadhar verification
and the other was probably for subsidy,
so I provide these two things
and after that I just
received the call 5 minutes ago, they are
coming for physical signature, so
we are fully absorbed in the next
week or whatever it is, within three to four to five days, it
seems that I will get the scooter,
friends, the call has come,
Thakur and I am waiting for physical signature  I'll download
them, I'm having a
little trouble giving their address, so let's see,
I have a little YouTube channel that will give
me a boost,
this is Anil Madhav, I want my own car,
Akshay,
I have two
[music],
Mukherjee is passing his age, you are
also making good live shows on YouTube, you will
edit
all the skins well,
I want you to come quickly and you should do it
properly, your
signature should be on every page,
finally you should keep your channel
well, if
that channel is a fitness channel then it is
okay, this is general,
now I put these and along with it whatever
blouse you can wash well,
now I follow this, then what
happens in it, then you will know, people have started in August
but they got it long ago and
I had said in the comment in July
when this repackaging stars Irfan, the pain is
true
and
here it will be that I have added a gun,
instead of sources, money in tears  It is that
stop the production of Aishwarya,
it has been looted, when I give thirty thousand
rupees extra then only they will make it great,
well they will convert this roti into pro
and understand that put the subscription,
now these pedos are pleased and
send the PAN card on the Aadhar card as well, make
163 digits, from then onwards it is not known, you
submit and you need
a spoon,
so friends, after the physical signature, we will
make its soft copy and share our love
and then there will be profit and
my scooter can be delivered in three to four days